Brock Fergus H Rupert **Fettes-Leagas**

Wantonwells Farm, Insch, Aberdeenshire, Scotland, AB52 6NL, UK

□+49 1577 649 1396 | ☑ fergusfettes@gmail.com | ☑ FergusFettes | 匝 fergus-fettes-433b46173

Summary_

MSc. in Physics with two years experience in hardware development for microscopy, fours years experience in software development (of which two years python) and one year experience as a DevOps engineer in a fast-growing multi-award-winning startup, transforming their services to a scalable microservices design. Happy working in a small, fast paced groups. Comfortable taking control of a project and bringing it to completion with autonomy.

Programming

SOME EXPERIENCE

- Javascript, HTML, CSS built a website with threejs: www.schau-wien.at
- · Matlab, LabView, Rust

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

• Python: - pandas, websockets, flask, pyaudio, pytest, cython

· Linux (bash and tmux scripting), Docker (docker-compose, Dockerfiles), K8s (Microk8s, GPU integration, GCS), Jenkins, Ansible

Work Experience _____

ONDEWO Vienna, Austria

PYTHON DEVELOPER

October 2019, present

- · Working with an award-winning Austrian startup developing a conversational AI platform for enabling human-machine interactions across mutliple sectors.
- · Integrating VOIP telephony into a live audio processing microservices architecture. Communicating over websockets/REST/GRPC with multiple third party providers.
- · Pro Dockerfile writer, docker-composer and eager experimenter with kubernetes (I run microk8s on my laptop for quick testing). Known for integrating current best practices in docker container design and streamlining CI/CD deployment (Jenkins).

Beas Botanics Aberdeen, Scotland

DATA ANALYST

Exploratory python work writing software for analysing ebay trends and creating automatic listings using the ebay API.

Molecular Biophysics (MBP, Seidel Lab), Universität Leipzig

Leipzig, Germany Apr. 2018 - Nov. 2018

April 2019 - July 2019

SOFTWARE/HARDWARE DEVELOPER

- Designed (with AutoCAD then in-house machining), assembled, developed software for (backend in LabView, data analysis in MATLAB/python) and finally tested a novel microscope setup for single molecule spectroscapy.
- Programming duties centered around particle tracking (machine vision) and UI development. It is currently in used for breakthrough CRISPR research.

Molecular Biophysics (MBP, Seidel Lab), Universität Leipzig

Leipzig, Germany

MATLAB DEVELOPER/ RESEARCH TECHNICIAN

- Jun. 2016 Apr. 2018
- · Studying DNA-protein intractions, including wetlab techniques, force microscopy and data analysis. Published with EMBOJ.
- Developed MATLAB software for streamlining data analysis.

Education

Universität Leipzig Leipzig, Germany

M.Sc. IN PHYSICS Apr. 2016 - Oct. 2018

Thesis topic: Development of a highly-parallel Magnetic Tweezers setup for Single Molecule Spectroscopy. Grade: 1,7 (good).

Open University Milton Keynes, England

B.Sc. IN NATURAL SCIENCES (PHYSICS)

Aug. 2013 - Mar. 2016

Thesis topic: literature review of novel sensors used in Magnetoencephalography (MEG)

AUGUST 23, 2020 FERGUS FETTES · RÉSUMÉ



__Schau Wien Vienna, Austria

Web Designer/Fullstack Engineer

March 2020 - present

• Founding member of an art collective in Vienna. Creating the website (pug/nodejs/threejs) and hosting stack (tried docker+GCS, moved on to static delivery with cloudflare).

• www.schau-wien.at

Python Bootcamp Auroville, India

PYTHON BACKEND DEVELOPER

Dec. 2018 - Jan. 2019

• Retraining in python backend development. Final project was an app for experimenting with cellular automata. https://github.com/FergusFettes/Lattice